[{"answer": "Well, this campaign is much more consequential than any couple of hires, but the reason he's risen in the polls is very simple.", "docId": "111212pmt", "aSentId": 25, "question": "So can we take the mere fact that you are on board as a sign that he's getting serious?", "qSentId": 24}, {"answer": "You know --", "docId": "111212pmt", "aSentId": 46, "question": "Are we really going to have the debate about who's the more -- reliable conservative if you're representing Governor Romney, Senator Talent?", "qSentId": 45}, {"answer": "Whoa, whoa.", "docId": "111212pmt", "aSentId": 59, "question": "Piers, can I answer that?", "qSentId": 58}, {"answer": "Well, look, this is a debate that we need to have.", "docId": "111212pmt", "aSentId": 85, "question": "You respond to what Kellyanne said, by all means, but also what are you going to do about the fact that all the momentum is now with your rival?", "qSentId": 84}, {"answer": "Well, we are.", "docId": "111212pmt", "aSentId": 125, "question": "Is Newt Gingrich really geared up, do you think, as the opponent, for the long haul?", "qSentId": 124}, {"answer": "He can and he has.", "docId": "111212pmt", "aSentId": 141, "question": "Do you think he can do that?", "qSentId": 140}, {"answer": "Well, I don't know if the gloves are off.", "docId": "111212pmt", "aSentId": 164, "question": "From your perspective, obviously, you have to remain fairly neutral at the moment, but how are you viewing the race as it's progressing?", "qSentId": 163}, {"answer": "I'm very well.", "docId": "111212pmt", "aSentId": 217, "question": "How are you, Piers?", "qSentId": 216}, {"answer": "I watched the debates, you know, on Saturday night.", "docId": "111212pmt", "aSentId": 244, "question": "I mean can you see any of the other candidates really making much of a push at this stage?", "qSentId": 243}, {"answer": "I think -- I think that's a pretty good assessment.", "docId": "111212pmt", "aSentId": 256, "question": "I mean what is your expert assessment of the two candidates?", "qSentId": 255}, {"answer": "Well, that's one of the things that you fear going into a debate.", "docId": "111212pmt", "aSentId": 272, "question": "And he just exacerbated that, didn't he?", "qSentId": 271}, {"answer": "I think that's absolutely right.", "docId": "111212pmt", "aSentId": 299, "question": "What are you seeing?", "qSentId": 298}, {"answer": "Well, I think --", "docId": "111212pmt", "aSentId": 325, "question": "Who would be, do you think?", "qSentId": 324}, {"answer": "He's somebody who has been around a long time and is good on TV, is good in debates and -- you know, but Mitt Romney has shown himself to be somebody who is good at politics as well.", "docId": "111212pmt", "aSentId": 360, "question": "What do you make of this surge by former Speaker Gingrich?", "qSentId": 359}, {"answer": "I would give them some advice.", "docId": "111212pmt", "aSentId": 368, "question": "Should we read into that that they're probably more worried about Newt Gingrich?", "qSentId": 367}, {"answer": "It sure was.", "docId": "111212pmt", "aSentId": 397, "question": "It was all a bit of a storm in a teacup, wasn't it?", "qSentId": 396}, {"answer": "I don't believe they do.", "docId": "111212pmt", "aSentId": 413, "question": "Do they?", "qSentId": 412}, {"answer": "Well, I think it's going to be really hard to follow Mike Bloomberg.", "docId": "111212pmt", "aSentId": 439, "question": "But what are your views generally about who the next mayor perhaps ought to be?", "qSentId": 438}, {"answer": "When I see a speech like that, it looks like he's getting ready to fight and take some numbers.", "docId": "111212pmt", "aSentId": 480, "question": "Where do you think he is right now, given all that's been going on?", "qSentId": 479}, {"answer": "I don't think it's going very well at all.", "docId": "111212pmt", "aSentId": 487, "question": "What do you think of the way their race is going?", "qSentId": 486}, {"answer": "I think people like Warren Buffett -- I'm not in his class.", "docId": "111212pmt", "aSentId": 499, "question": "It seems a bit trite to say that, because in any kind of society where you have this kind of financial meltdown, isn't it instinctively the right thing not do, that the rich should contribute a little bit more to the recovery than those with no money?", "qSentId": 498}, {"answer": "I'm a movie maker.", "docId": "111212pmt", "aSentId": 509, "question": "Who do you think is going to be the Republican nominee, as we sit here today?", "qSentId": 508}, {"answer": "Here's how it happens -- this is -- this is where King Solomon taught me a great lesson.", "docId": "111212pmt", "aSentId": 538, "question": "So what do you want to win?", "qSentId": 537}, {"answer": "Tell me about Margaret Thatcher.", "docId": "111212pmt", "aSentId": 548, "question": "Wouldn't that be a nice night if they both won?", "qSentId": 547}, {"answer": "Listen, that's a sexy, fun, entertaining movie.", "docId": "111212pmt", "aSentId": 601, "question": "What did you think of that?", "qSentId": 600}]